Abdalsalam Al Birawi

I am a Front-End engineer with good experience in problem solving, and experience in UI/UX. Always striving to become a better web developer. Friendly, professional, Able to work alone or in groups, and under pressure.

Syria/Aleppo/Al Zahra +963 932 583 562 abdalsalamalbirawi@amail.com

<u>linkedin.com/in/abdalsalam-albir</u> <u>awi</u>

aithub.com/AbdulsalamBirawi

WORK EXPERIENCE

FreeLance Web Developer | 2021 - present

- Working on a range of freelance web projects
- Proficient in HTML,CSS,REACT.
- Maintained applications and updated them.
- Able to identify problems and bugs in the code and quickly resolve the problem.

Volunteering, Syria — BlueBits (technical Member)

I was a volunteer in blue bits team as a technical member for five years. BlueBits team is a volunteering team that helps students in all aspects of their college life, such as writing lectures and helping them to prepare for exams. It was a great experience from which I learned many techniques that helped me to become a better developer.

Mayar World, Ankara, Turkey | 2/2019 - 2/2020

Front-End web developer

I worked with mayar world as a front-end web developer, and it was my first real world experience, I have learned many things.

AbdulQader_Q@hotmail.com

EDUCATION

Aleppo University, Bachelor in Computer Engineering.

Sep 2017 - Sep 2022

PROJECTS

Cryptocurrency website. Using react and ant design **Real estate website.** A real estate website for rent and purchase in the UAE developed in next.js and chakraUI.

STACK

Proficient: Javascript, TypeScript, React, Next.js, Material UI

Familiar: C++

AWARDS

My graduation project was the best in the faculty with 98% grade, and it was nominated for the Syrian competition for best projects.

LANGUAGES

Arabic native

English B2 (Upper-Intermediate

English)

German A1, beginner